cigartrade.net 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy

SHOPPING CART

The cart is empty

##  Privacy Policy 

Cigartrade.net, takes your privacy seriously and is committed to protecting the personal information that you provide to us. This Privacy statement covers our website, www.Cigartrade.net, and explains our policies and practices regarding the use and disclosure of your personal information collected by us.

cigartrade.net reviews and updates this policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, we advise you to review this policy periodically. By using our website you consent to the terms of this policy. 

Personal Information

In general, you can visit our website without explicitly providing us any personal information. However, certain services offered on this website may require you to enter varying amount of a user's personal information. This information includes user registration data such as user's name, phone number, Email address, city etc. In addition, as with many other web servers, we may also collect and log tracking information via website request data and response data. This policy applies to all information (User Information) collected by the Website. 

Use of Personal Information

cigartrade.net is committed to the privacy of the User Information collected by the Website and will not transfer any personal information to any outside parties. Any requested information is for internal cigartrade.net use only. We do not share any information about individual users or the organizations they represent for marketing purposes with any third party, under no circumstances.

cigartrade.net opposes the emailing of any junk mail, and does not sell user information to email lists or telemarketers. If you receive junk email that mentions the Website services, please email to [support@cigartrade.net](mailto:support@cigartrade.net) and we will make a prompt investigation.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

External Links

Our Website may also provide links to other websites that are either owned or operated by cigartrade.net or other third-party websites. Such external websites have their own privacy policies separate from this policy. Even if the third party is affiliated with cigartrade.net through a business partnership or otherwise, cigartrade.net is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. All external links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and you access them at your own risk.

Terms of Use

We encourage you to also see our Legal Notice, which describes the restrictions, disclaimers, indemnification and limitation of liability governing the use of the entire cigartrade.net Website.

Contact Information

Please Contact Us if you have any questions or suggestions regarding this policy statement.
